<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Protect Pet</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="google_maps_key">AIzaSyAM4lX9nQvqwEDXGcohIY61cw3kUqBeIxU</string>
    <string name="pass_hint">Password...</string>
    <string name="email_hint">Your Email...</string>
    <string name="login_logo_desc">Logo Login Page</string>
    <string name="login_btn_text">Login</string>
    <string name="login_reg_btn_text">SignUp?</string>
    <string name="action_search_text">Search</string>
    <string name="action_setting_text">Account Settings</string>
    <string name="action_logout_text">Logout</string>
    <string name="reg_btn_text">Create new Account</string>
    <string name="reg_login_text">Login?</string>
    <string name="reg_pass_text">Password...</string>
    <string name="reg_confirm_pass_text">Confirm Password...</string>
    <string name="setup_name_hint">Your Name...</string>
    <string name="setup_save_btn">Save Account Settings</string>
    <string name="setup_name_hint_text">Your Name ...</string>
    <string name="setup_btn_name_text">Save Account Settings</string>
    <string name="post_desc_hint">Add Description ...</string>
    <string name="new_post_btn_hint">Post</string>
    <string name="bottom_home_text">Home</string>
    <string name="bottom_notification_text">Notification</string>
    <string name="bottom_ac_text">Account</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="sure_text">Are You Sure?</string>
    <!--Misc texts-->
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot password?</string>
    <string name="no_account">Don\’t have an account?</string>
    <string name="have_account">Have an account?</string>
    <string name="login_btn_label">Login</string>
    <string name="signup_btn_label">Signup</string>

    <string name="login_label">" Login"</string>
    <string name="signup_label">" Signup"</string>
    <string name="options">Adopt</string>

    <string-array name="options">
        <item>Adopt</item>
        <item>Rescue</item>
        <item>Random</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="nearby_option">

        <item>Select Nearby Category</item>
        <item>Pharmacy</item>
        <item>Food Shop</item>
        <item>Hospital</item>
        <item>Doctor</item>


    </string-array>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="aboutus"> We have tried to Build a community where people value animals and treat them well with respect and proper care.
        We tried to Gather volunteers to help the helpless, needy, abandoned animals and Providing information on medical resources for animals.
        It is a social-communicative site where pet owners, helpers, experts, rescuers can communicate and help each other effortlessly.
        This app will help tracking details on birth, food habit, growth and medical history of a pet.
        And also useful for Reducing pet overpopulation and suffering.</string>

    <string name="vaccine">This is vaccine instruction</string>
    <string name="petcare">Having a pet sounds interesting and fun. But, adopting a pet and taking care of them is a big
        responsibility. Here are some of the tips which will help you to take good care of your pet and keep them happy,
        active and healthy:</string>

    <string name="dog">Provide a protected and clean living environment for your dog. Always keep fresh water available.
        Feed a quality diet and prevent obesity. Have your pet examined by a veterinarian on a regular basis. Provide ample opportunities to exercise.
        Communicate with your dog and develop a relationship. Train your dog to follow the simple commands. Practice reproductive control.
        Don’t overlook grooming and nail trimming and dental care is very important.</string>
    <string name="bird">As long as you know how to look after a bird properly, your home can be a wonderful place for your pet to live, flourish and fly!
        Make sure your pet bird has access to bird baths or showers. They love water and it’s great for keeping them healthy and happy.
        Give them access to full sunlight and 10-12 hours of darkness every night. This can be made easier to achieve with a blackout cover.
        Let them get some exercise. Use toys to keep them active in their cage and supervise out-of-cage play at least once a week. Make sure you choose
        a safe location for them to spread their wings and keep them on a harness if necessary.</string>
    <string name="cat">Provide plenty of human companionship.
        Provide regular, suitable meals with a constant supply of fresh water.
        Provide a clean and comfortable bed.
        Provide the cat with outdoor access or be prepared to empty and clean a litter tray on a daily basis.
        Provide it with a stimulating and safe environment.
        Groom it regularly. Longhaired cats require daily grooming.
        Have it neutered between 4 and 6 months old.
        Vaccinate against the major feline diseases regularly.
        Worm regularly and provide treatment for fleas.
        Take the cat to the vet when it shows any sign of illness.
        Insure your cat or make sure you can afford the cost of any veterinary treatment it may need.</string>

    <string name="title_activity_address_map">Map</string>

</resources>
